sweetiessweeps.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | SweetiesSweeps.com

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/sweetiessweeps.com).  

 **Privacy Policy for Sweeties Sweeps  
**

These policies are valid from June 24, 2008 and were updated December 5, 2015. Updated on May 24, 2018

**Commitment to Online Security**

Personal information submitted to Sweeties Sweeps is only accessible only the owners of this site.

**Affiliate and Tracking Links Policies**

Sweeties Sweeps uses affiliate and tracking links in our posts, sweepstakes listings and on social media. Affiliate links help us generate income to keep SweetiesSweeps.com free for the public to use. If you do not like ads, please consider joining our private, member only site, Sweeties Secret Sweeps. There are no ads on the Secret site and all sweepstakes found on SweetiesSweeps.com can also be found on [Sweeties Secret Sweeps](http://sweetiessecretsweeps.com/join/) along with up to bonus member-only sweepstakes each month that are never listed on SweetiesSweeps.com.

Sweeties Sweeps uses Amazon affiliate links in some of the posts and sweepstakes listings. If you click that link and go to Amazon to look at a product and make a purchase of that product or other products up to 30 days, we may make a commission on that sale. You are never required to purchase anything by using our link. We use Amazon affiliate links to help generate income for SweetiesSweeps.com. By clicking the link and shopping as normal you are helping us to generate the income we need to keep SweetiesSweeps.com free to use. Free sites cannot run without some form of income. We do not use affiliate links on Sweeties Secret Sweeps.

If a company asks us to list a sweepstakes they may ask us to use tracking link so they can track how much traffic is coming from the Secret site to their entry page. This tracking link is totally anonymous and does not contain any of your personal information.

You can read our full Ad and Affiliate Policies [here](http://sweetiessweeps.com/about/product-review-and-ad-policies)

**Referral Links**

As of February 26, 2018, we do not use referral links in the sweepstakes listed on SweetiesSweeps.com (our public, free site) or in our social media posts on Facebook or Twitter. We also do not use referral links in any of the member-only, private content on SweetiesSecretSweeps.com (read the policies [here](https://sweetiessecretsweeps.com/sweeties-secret-sweeps-policies) for the Secret site). However, members are allowed to add their own referral links in the private area of SweetiesSecretSweeps.com.

**Personal Information Collected at** **Sweeties Sweeps**

Sweeties Sweeps may ask you to provide the following types of personal information: name, postal address, email addresses, and phone numbers. This information is given freely by you and is not required to view, read, or use this site. Sweeties Sweeps may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information such as the date of your visit to the site, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP, Mac OS, etc.), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Comcast, etc.), and the IP Address of your computer.

Sweeties Sweeps does not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 18 without the expressed permission from a parent or legal guardian, and the site is not structured to attract anyone under the age of 18.

**How Sweeties Sweeps** **Uses Personal Information Collected Online**

Sweeties Sweeps will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to reply to inquiries and comments, provide operational notices, publish a newsletter, and program or sweepstakes participation. By completing an entry or registration form you are allowing us store your information in a database for retrieval at a future time for purposes of picking a winner for a giveaway or contacting you with site updates.

Sweeties Sweeps will never sell, rent or share your personal information with third-parties.

This blog is hosted by Rack Space on a dedicated server.

In general, you are responsible for the information you submit in the form of a comment on a post on this blog. Your comments can be read by anyone and your profile can be viewed by anyone. You are allowed to post as an Anonymous reader as a way to help protect your privacy.

Read about our Ad and Affiliate Policies [here](http://sweetiessweeps.com/about/product-review-and-ad-policies)

**Materials Submitted to Sweeties Sweeps**

All photos, written correspondence and any other materials submitted to Sweeties Sweeps become the sole and exclusive property of Sweeties Sweeps and cannot be returned at any time. By submitting Materials, you agree that Sweeties Sweeps may, but is not obligated to, use the Materials in connection with the site, in any way, in any medium, worldwide, in perpetuity. Further, you warrant all Materials are 100% original and do not violate the right of privacy or publicity of, or constitute a defamation against, any person or entity; that the Materials will not infringe upon or violate the copyright or common law rights or any other rights of any person or entity; that there are and will be no encumbrances, liens, conditions or restrictions whatsoever upon or affecting such Materials; and that you and the person depicted in the Materials are at least 18 years of age or you are a parent or guardian granting permission for use. You agree to indemnify Sweeties Sweeps for all damages and expenses (including reasonable attorney’s fees) arising out of any breach or failure of the warranties made herein.

**Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate**

If your personal information changes please submit the changes to Sweeties Sweeps by email at [sweetiessweeps@gmail.com](mailto:sweetiessweeps@gmail.com). Please be sure to note that you are “updating” your information.

**Computer Tracking and Cookies**

Our site is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. Our website also recognizes the online site where a visitor clicked one of our banners or buttons to follow through and visit our site, but we cannot identify the visitor or the visitor’s address. Site information is used to confirm promotion of Sweeties Sweeps giveaways, newsletter, or other projects, and may be used to advise participants of the numbers of visitors who come to our site from their sites. No personal information is collected.

**Third Party Ads**

Sweeties Sweeps use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) or [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

_Sweeties Sweeps cannot be responsible for content provided in these ads and what you, as the visitors of Sweeties Sweeps, does once you leave SweetiesSweeps.com. Please protect yourself by being an informed consumer and read the information presented to you carefully._

**Disclaimer Policy**

This blog contains links to other websites and blogs. All external links contain content which is not endorsed or controlled by this blog. All information that you submit on other websites is done so at your own risk. If you are concerned about the sites you visit from this please read the “Privacy Policy” of each website or blog you visit.

**Disclosure Policy**

Sweeties Sweeps may accept forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions, affiliate advertising, or other forms of compensation from time to time. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

As the owner of this blog I may be compensated from time to time to provide opinions on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though we may receive compensations for posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely our own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question directly.

Your feedback and assistance is welcome in updating the information on this site if you find updates or errors.

**Email Services**

We use MailChimp to manage our email marketing subscriber list and to send emails to our subscribers. MailChimp is a third-party provider, which may process your data using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our newsletter.

MailChimp’s privacy policy is available at [www.mailchimp.com/legal](https://www.mailchimp.com/legal)

You can unsubscribe from our newsletter by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided at the end of each newsletter.
